http://www.jadesterling.com/privacy-policy/

Material Safety Data Sheet
Search for:
HomeQuality
Cold Heading Quality RodIndustrial Quality RodMerchant Bar QualityMerchant Quality RodSpecial Bar Quality
HomeQuality
Cold Heading Quality RodIndustrial Quality RodMerchant Bar QualityMerchant Quality RodSpecial Bar Quality
HomeQuality
Cold Heading Quality RodIndustrial Quality RodMerchant Bar QualityMerchant Quality RodSpecial Bar Quality
February 18, 2013 by Hiep Nguyen
Thank you for your interest in Jade-Sterling Steel Co. Inc., and welcome to our Web site. Because we know that you are concerned about privacy, we have established the Privacy Policy set forth below concerning the personal information that you provide to us online. We want you to know and be comfortable about how your personal information may be collected, used and stored, as well as the security aspects related to your use of our site and linked sites. Finally, we want to give you a contact for any questions or concerns that you may have about any of these matters after reading our Privacy Policy.
In summary, Jade-Sterling’s policy is to collect, store and use such information only to the extent permitted by and in full compliance with applicable law.
By using our Web site in accordance with our Privacy Policy, you consent to the collection, storage and use of any information that you provide to Jade-Sterling or that is provided by your use. Jade-Sterling may modify its Privacy Policy from time to time. If we do, we will post changes on this page. Your continued use of our Web site following the posting of changes to the Privacy Policy will mean that you accept the changes.
Questions regarding this policy should be directed to support@jadesterling.com.
Collection, Storage and Use of Information
Jade-Sterling will not collect personal information about you (for example, your name, address, or telephone number) unless you provide it voluntarily during your use of our site or by sending us an e-mail. If you do not want this information to be collected by us, please do not submit it. In the course of using our site, however, we automatically track certain information about you. For example, this information includes the URL that you just came from (whether this URL is on our site or not), which URL you go to next (whether this URL is on our site or not), what browser you are using, and your IP address. Many sites automatically collect this kind of information.
We use the information that you provide by using our site to help us improve our services to you, to furnish you with the products that you have requested, to inform you about additional products or services that may be of interest to you, for marketing purposes and for other internal purposes. Jade-Sterling Steel has no plans to sell, trade or rent your personal information to anyone.
External Web Sites
Jade-Sterling Steel its discretion may choose from time to time to link to third party Web sites. Such links do not constitute an endorsement of such third party Web sites. To the extent hyperlinks or banner advertisements incorporating hyperlinks are utilized to access third party Web sites, you should be aware that they are not controlled by Jade-Sterling Steel and, therefore, are not subject to this Privacy Policy, nor is Jade-Sterling Steel responsible for any viruses, content or disputes resulting from your access to such sites. You should check the privacy policies of each of those sites to see how your personal information will be utilized by their operators.
How to Contact Us
Should you have other questions or concerns about this Privacy Policy or about Jade-Sterling’s Web site, please send us an e-mail at support@jadesterling.com.
Who We AreDistributors of Round Steel Bar Stock and Wire Rod
